[{"answer": "It was an unbelievable day.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What was it like for you?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, I don't like to use the word closure.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "I mean, Commissioner, did you get a sense of your men, that these brave firemen feeling any sense of closure or is it not really that kind of emotion?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "I spoke to many firefighters today, and they all feel like I feel, that we go along with the decision of the president.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Yes, I mean, do you think New York firemen would like to see a picture of a dead Osama bin Laden?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "It doesn't surprise me one bit, Piers.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "When you hear that, what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I'm pleased that he will no longer be around to do any harm to anybody.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Were you pleased when you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, personally, I don't need to see that.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What did you think of the decision not to publish the images of a dead bin Laden?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I'm vociferous in my skepticism of those who don't tell the truth and who have a track record of not telling the truth.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Why would you simply believe what they tell you on this?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, he hasn't done it yet.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "I mean, when he said, before he was elected, that he would close down Guantanamo Bay, and then he doesn't do that, I mean, that's not entirely being straight with you, is it?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I just -- I think that -- and I don't think I'm the only one who feels this way.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "But if he was executed, is that lawful or would you have preferred him to have been captured alive and brought back to trial maybe in New York?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "OORE: Right next door to it.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "What do you think about the fact that bin Laden appears to have been there for up to five years, in this large property right next to Pakistanis' military intelligence?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I would like to know that.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Would you go further and say that President Obama or his intelligence advisers -- are you suggesting that any of them had knowledge for a considerable period of time?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Would you know --", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I think there are a lot of people running around calling themselves al Qaeda.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Well, you don't believe al Qaeda exists in any form?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, I think, listen, actually, the day that al Qaeda was dismantled, personally, frankly, what I think, it was the day that the revolution began in Tunisia.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Do you believe al Qaeda has been dismantled?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, he inherited a huge mess.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Are you slightly more critical there?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Not one.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Not one?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "I hope in this coming election year that people remember that -- not just Donald Trump, but a majority of the people who called themselves Republicans said that they didn't believe or they weren't sure that President Obama was an American.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "But when you see the Donald Trump Birther issue dominating the news agenda, and there was a real prospect of perhaps Donald Trump running for president, what was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, that's a much larger issue than the way that he was just kind of simplifying it.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "But when he was coming out with stuff about China and OPEC and so on, I actually found myself nodding in agreement, that America has been pretty weak in relation to OPEC and China, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well, I don't talk to my next project while I'm doing it for all the obvious reasons.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What is the next cage that you're going to rattle?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I'm afraid it was a beauty and the beast situation, so the beast has to leave the stage.", "docId": "110505pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Is that correct?", "qSentId": 442}]